# Sabastian Storm White Belser, MBA

sswbelser.com sswbelser@gmail.com (510) 847-6982 linkedin.com/in/sswbelser github.com/sswbelser @sswbelser

## PERSONAL STATEMENT

I have worked several years in human resources and operations. I have a proven track record both as an HR Generalist and Recruiter, I have worked in a wide array of different environments, I have managed teams of over 30 employees, I am a fast learner, and I am a hobbyist software/game developer. My education and unique work experiences make me a great fit for a company seeking an HR professional who speaks the language of developers.

### **EDUCATION**

2015

General Assembly, San Francisco Web Development Immersive

2014

Golden Gate University, San Francisco
MBA: Management / Information Systems

2012

University of California, Davis BA: Sociology / Organizational Studies

### **SKILLS**

HRMS/ ATS Administration Benefits Administration Full-Cycle Recruiting Onboarding/Offboarding Workers' Compensation Conducting Interviews Internal Training Performance Reviews
People/Project Management
Business Analytics
Forecasting/Budgeting
Operations Management
Software Development
Game Development

## **EXPERIENCE**

# **General Assembly**

Front End Development TA | 2015-Current

- Assisting head instructor with teaching various front end languages, frameworks, and libraries
- Leading discussion groups/stand-ups on specific topics
- Offering one-on-one mentorship to students as needed
- Keeping tabs on students' progress

# Web Development Immersive Student | 2015-2015

- Interviewed by Wall Street Journal about my projects
- Pair programming, working with teams, agile development

## **GHD Inc.**

### Human Resources Generalist | 2014-2015

- HRIS & ATS: PeopleSoft, ADP, Taleo, e-learning, and legacy systems
- Administered e-learning systems
- Facilitated new hire orientations
- Managed the onboarding and offboarding processes
- Resolved staff conflicts/inquiries
- Process analyses and consolidation for company merger

# **Bauer's Intelligent Transportation**

Account Manager | 2013-2014

- Managed operations of the UC Berkeley bus system
- Project management to increase operational efficiency

# **Berkshire Hathaway Homestate Companies**

Human Resources Assistant | 2012-2013

- HRIS & ATS: ADP, SharedHR, Workday, and legacy systems
- Recruited various technical and non-technical positions including the company's new CIO - for various offices across the country
- Conducted applicant phone screens and assessment tests
- Administrated benefits through various vendors
- Managed the onboarding and offboarding processes
- Facilitated new hire orientations
- Training upper management on systems/functionalities
- Hired, trained, and supervised the internship program

# **Specialized Transportation Services/Tipsy Taxi**

Director | 2009-2012

- Hired, trained, and mentored ~30 direct reports
- Responsible for all operations and finances
- Rolled out sweeping operations and administrative changes, which resulted in much a higher revenue
- Worked with various government bodies on grants for large capital purchases

#### **Unitrans**

## Planning Manager / Outreach & Retention Coordinator | 2008-2012

- After starting as a bus driver, I held various part time leadership and management roles at Unitrans
- Supervised ~15 office clerks and planning assistants
- Managed and resolved all customer complaints
- Assisted in implementing new NextBus tracking system both customer-facing and internal functionalities
- Recruited all student positions sourced resumes, scheduled/conducted interviews, etc.